

FRONTEND DEVELOPER

CONTACT

artur.jedrzejczak@gmail.com



+48 664 289 281



Poznan, Poland



github.com/aratur



linkedin.com/in/artur-jedrzejczak

SKILLS

Frontend: React, React Router, React Query,

Redux Toolkit, React Testing Library, Material UI, JavaScript, TypeScript, HTML, CSS, SASS,

Jest, NodeJS, Electron

Databases: Oracle DB, MS SQL Server,

MySQL, SQLite

Tools: Git, GitHub, Bitbucket, Jira,

DevTools, Postman, JMeter

IDE: Visual Studio Code, Atom, IntelliJ

EDUCATION

Poznań University of Economics Master's Degree, Information Systems [2004 - 2009]

CERTIFICATION

- Oracle DB SQL Certified Expert
- Oracle Certified Associate, Java SE 8 Programmer
- IBM Data Science Professional Certificate
- Professional Scrum Master (PSM I)

PROFILE SUMMARY

Developer with almost 15 years of experience working with different technologies (over 2 years frontend) looking for a role as a mid/senior developer. Motivated, with willingness to learn new technologies and skills. Good team worker. Open to a B2B or an employment contract, remote work. Due to personal reasons a 4 day working week is preferred. Currently on a B2B contract, with a 14 days notice period.

EXPERIENCE

07/2020 - PRESENT SENIOR DEVELOPER AT CAPCO POLAND SP. Z O.O.

Project: Back-office application for HSBC

Responsibilities: Development of a fronted, banking applications for back-office employees. **Technologies:** React, Redux Toolkit, React Router, React Testing Library, Material UI,

JavaScript, TypeScript, SASS, CSS, HTML

07/2020 - PRESENT PERSONAL FRONTED DEVELOPMENT MASTERY PATH

Project: Personal frontend projects

Responsibilities: To show some of my work I've built several sites that are available on my

portfolio page. This is because what I normally do is not publicly available. They have live versions, and links to the source code, so feel free to take a

look.

First are from the time when I started working with React. Recent ones are based on Figma design files from frontendmentor.io (using ready designs allowed me to focus more on the implementation side of things).

Technologies: React, Redux Toolkit, React Router, React Query, React Testing Library, JavaScript, TypeScript, CSS, SASS, HTML, Material UI, Vite, Parcel

06/2017 - 07/2020 SENIOR DEVELOPER AT CAPCO POLAND SP. Z O.O.

Project: New internet banking for BNP Paribas Polska

Responsibilities: Building migration engines for Identity Management System and Payments

Implementation of micro-services in the area of system administration,

payments

Technologies: Oracle SQL, Java, Spring Boot, Hibernate, JMeter

11/2015 - 02/2017 CONSULTANT AT ACCENTURE SP. Z 0.0.

Project: Building a new Digital Bank in France for La Banque Postale based on mBank. **Responsibilities** Designing an architecture of payments and cards for the new bank using a fit-

gap approach.

Technologies: APIs, UML, software architecture

SEE MY PORTFOLIO





aj-cv.vercel.app/portfolio

01/2015 - 07/2015

CONSULTANT AT ACCENTURE SP. Z O.O.

Project: Post-merger integration for mBank and BRE Bank

Responsibilities Implementation of Migration engine, Implementation of synchronization tool

between SharePoint and MS Project to track live-progress and reporting.

Technologies: C#, MS SQL Server, MS Project, SharePoint

03/2013 - 12/2014

CONSULTANT AT ACCENTURE SP. Z O.O.

Project: Post-merger integration for Santander Bank Polska and Kredyt Bank

Responsibilities Implementation of Migration engine in Loans area including reconciliation.

Technologies: Ab Initio (ETL), MySQL

12/2010 - 11/2013

ANALYST AT ACCENTURE SP. Z O.O.

Project: Flexcube Core Banking system implementation for DNB Nord

Responsibilities Operational reports delivery in loans area. Development of post-migration

reconciliation reports for corporate loans. Implementation of interface

between the Lithuanian Central Bank.

Technologies: SQL Server, Oracle DBL

08/2008 - 11/2010

DEVELOPMENT SPECIALIST AT BZ WBK S.A.

Project: Transfer Agent implementation for Arka Investment Funds

Responsibilities Implementation of reconciliation reporting, and business reporting

Technologies: Oracle, Business Objects

Wyrażam zgodę na przetwarzanie moich danych osobowych dla potrzeb niezbędnych do realizacji procesu rekrutacji (zgodnie z ustawą z dnia 10 maja 2018 roku o ochronie danych osobowych (Dz. Ustaw z 2018, poz. 1000) oraz zgodnie z Rozporządzeniem Parlamentu Europejskiego i Rady (UE) 2016/679 z dnia 27 kwietnia 2016 r. w sprawie ochrony osób fizycznych w związku z przetwarzaniem danych osobowych i w sprawie swobodnego przepływu takich danych oraz uchylenia dyrektywy 95/46/WE (RODO).
Wyrażam zgodę na przetwarzanie moich danych osobowych w zakresie przyszłych procesów rekrutacyjnych.